<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://theme236-wood-finishes.myshopify.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme236-wood-finishes.myshopify.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://theme236-wood-finishes.myshopify.com/blogs/news/tagged/behlen.atom"/>
  <title>WOODWORK - Blog</title>
  <updated>2016-03-01T03:42:30-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>WOODWORK</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://theme236-wood-finishes.myshopify.com/blogs/news/90456321-how-to-install-wood-stairs</id>
    <published>2016-03-01T03:32:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2016-03-01T03:32:30-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://theme236-wood-finishes.myshopify.com/blogs/news/90456321-how-to-install-wood-stairs"/>
    <title>How to Install Wood Stairs</title>
    <author>
      <name>David Braun</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>To install a staircase that will be functional, decorative, and safe, certain guidelines must be observed.</p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><strong>Our goods will help you protect any type of wooden surface from multitude harmful factors of environment saving its initial appearance and beauty</strong></p>
<p>There is no wooden item that can be done properly without a suitable finish use. Applying a finish to wooden surface you prolong its term of use and prevent it from swelling and cracking. Wooden surface will please you for a long time having a look of a just done product, no matter how old it will be. Without a finish your wood can dry and become deformed turning your furniture into repulsive looking and useless. But not every finish will be a suitable one for all wooden surface types.</p>
<ul>
<li>Anchorseal</li>
<li>Behlen</li>
<li>Earlex</li>
<li>Lancaster</li>
<li>Norton</li>
</ul>
<p>Your furniture needs a professional approach to achieve you the desired result. Our Wood Finishes Store offers a wide range of all possible finishes and we will help you choose the needed one. We have finishes to dry the wood inside (penetrating finishes) and on the surface (surface finishes). Our products are divided in accordance with these two main principles and in accordance with the following use of a wooden item. Thus you will easily find the needed product just following our categories which will be your guiding lines to the very finish you are looking for.</p>
<p>Our Wood Finishes Store will become your reliable assistant offering goods of a premium quality and the leading trading marks.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
